[
    {
        "question": "1 + 8 = ?",
        "answers": [
            6,
            16,
            9,
            14
        ],
        "correct": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 20 = ?",
        "answers": [
            34,
            33,
            43,
            40
        ],
        "correct": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 5 = ?",
        "answers": [
            15,
            16,
            6,
            12
        ],
        "correct": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 4 = ?",
        "answers": [
            16,
            23,
            13,
            21
        ],
        "correct": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 11 = ?",
        "answers": [
            21,
            11,
            15,
            19
        ],
        "correct": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 8 = ?",
        "answers": [
            29,
            36,
            17,
            26
        ],
        "correct": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 1 = ?",
        "answers": [
            1,
            11,
            7,
            18
        ],
        "correct": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 1 = ?",
        "answers": [
            29,
            26,
            20,
            18
        ],
        "correct": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 18 = ?",
        "answers": [
            30,
            35,
            33,
            29
        ],
        "correct": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 12 = ?",
        "answers": [
            31,
            41,
            21,
            35
        ],
        "correct": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 4 = ?",
        "answers": [
            17,
            28,
            25,
            22
        ],
        "correct": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 11 = ?",
        "answers": [
            21,
            24,
            19,
            17
        ],
        "correct": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 20 = ?",
        "answers": [
            35,
            27,
            28,
            18
        ],
        "correct": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 2 = ?",
        "answers": [
            3,
            13,
            0,
            -2
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 18 = ?",
        "answers": [
            46,
            38,
            28,
            30
        ],
        "correct": 38
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 20 = ?",
        "answers": [
            31,
            40,
            49,
            35
        ],
        "correct": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 6 = ?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            34,
            25,
            28
        ],
        "correct": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 6 = ?",
        "answers": [
            15,
            14,
            20,
            11
        ],
        "correct": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 10 = ?",
        "answers": [
            27,
            21,
            8,
            17
        ],
        "correct": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 18 = ?",
        "answers": [
            41,
            39,
            36,
            31
        ],
        "correct": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 19 = ?",
        "answers": [
            23,
            14,
            18,
            32
        ],
        "correct": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 2 = ?",
        "answers": [
            8,
            -5,
            7,
            4
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 12 = ?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            20,
            14,
            21
        ],
        "correct": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 3 = ?",
        "answers": [
            19,
            4,
            6,
            14
        ],
        "correct": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 16 = ?",
        "answers": [
            22,
            21,
            25,
            29
        ],
        "correct": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 9 = ?",
        "answers": [
            25,
            24,
            33,
            23
        ],
        "correct": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 18 = ?",
        "answers": [
            33,
            27,
            24,
            28
        ],
        "correct": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 5 = ?",
        "answers": [
            25,
            17,
            29,
            32
        ],
        "correct": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 10 = ?",
        "answers": [
            25,
            27,
            22,
            20
        ],
        "correct": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 14 = ?",
        "answers": [
            23,
            32,
            25,
            29
        ],
        "correct": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 13 = ?",
        "answers": [
            24,
            23,
            22,
            33
        ],
        "correct": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 12 = ?",
        "answers": [
            36,
            35,
            37,
            27
        ],
        "correct": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 15 = ?",
        "answers": [
            36,
            20,
            28,
            29
        ],
        "correct": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 9 = ?",
        "answers": [
            16,
            20,
            19,
            13
        ],
        "correct": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 19 = ?",
        "answers": [
            29,
            18,
            28,
            27
        ],
        "correct": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 12 = ?",
        "answers": [
            20,
            31,
            22,
            26
        ],
        "correct": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 11 = ?",
        "answers": [
            36,
            30,
            20,
            28
        ],
        "correct": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 8 = ?",
        "answers": [
            17,
            22,
            19,
            27
        ],
        "correct": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 7 = ?",
        "answers": [
            22,
            31,
            29,
            17
        ],
        "correct": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 3 = ?",
        "answers": [
            15,
            23,
            11,
            19
        ],
        "correct": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 20 = ?",
        "answers": [
            31,
            29,
            35,
            25
        ],
        "correct": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 12 = ?",
        "answers": [
            28,
            35,
            29,
            25
        ],
        "correct": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 18 = ?",
        "answers": [
            15,
            25,
            17,
            19
        ],
        "correct": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 14 = ?",
        "answers": [
            23,
            9,
            18,
            20
        ],
        "correct": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 14 = ?",
        "answers": [
            11,
            22,
            19,
            21
        ],
        "correct": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 17 = ?",
        "answers": [
            40,
            44,
            36,
            27
        ],
        "correct": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 14 = ?",
        "answers": [
            35,
            34,
            42,
            32
        ],
        "correct": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 19 = ?",
        "answers": [
            32,
            27,
            39,
            40
        ],
        "correct": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 5 = ?",
        "answers": [
            25,
            21,
            23,
            35
        ],
        "correct": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 3 = ?",
        "answers": [
            3,
            2,
            16,
            9
        ],
        "correct": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 7 = ?",
        "answers": [
            8,
            17,
            3,
            -1
        ],
        "correct": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 8 = ?",
        "answers": [
            25,
            26,
            17,
            34
        ],
        "correct": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 5 = ?",
        "answers": [
            21,
            17,
            19,
            16
        ],
        "correct": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 7 = ?",
        "answers": [
            13,
            31,
            16,
            22
        ],
        "correct": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 5 = ?",
        "answers": [
            10,
            9,
            0,
            19
        ],
        "correct": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 9 = ?",
        "answers": [
            23,
            14,
            22,
            13
        ],
        "correct": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 9 = ?",
        "answers": [
            30,
            36,
            29,
            20
        ],
        "correct": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 4 = ?",
        "answers": [
            11,
            10,
            8,
            7
        ],
        "correct": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 5 = ?",
        "answers": [
            24,
            28,
            19,
            16
        ],
        "correct": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 16 = ?",
        "answers": [
            42,
            26,
            30,
            34
        ],
        "correct": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 7 = ?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            14,
            10,
            12
        ],
        "correct": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 3 = ?",
        "answers": [
            15,
            8,
            16,
            6
        ],
        "correct": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 12 = ?",
        "answers": [
            21,
            17,
            23,
            16
        ],
        "correct": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 12 = ?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            11,
            24,
            20
        ],
        "correct": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 7 = ?",
        "answers": [
            6,
            7,
            5,
            9
        ],
        "correct": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 13 = ?",
        "answers": [
            11,
            18,
            15,
            20
        ],
        "correct": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 4 = ?",
        "answers": [
            17,
            18,
            21,
            15
        ],
        "correct": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 12 = ?",
        "answers": [
            29,
            21,
            38,
            36
        ],
        "correct": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 2 = ?",
        "answers": [
            16,
            14,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "correct": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 18 = ?",
        "answers": [
            32,
            37,
            40,
            22
        ],
        "correct": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 8 = ?",
        "answers": [
            28,
            22,
            19,
            33
        ],
        "correct": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 16 = ?",
        "answers": [
            22,
            12,
            21,
            29
        ],
        "correct": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 14 = ?",
        "answers": [
            29,
            28,
            18,
            26
        ],
        "correct": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 14 = ?",
        "answers": [
            10,
            26,
            17,
            19
        ],
        "correct": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 19 = ?",
        "answers": [
            33,
            28,
            30,
            35
        ],
        "correct": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 15 = ?",
        "answers": [
            20,
            28,
            16,
            14
        ],
        "correct": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 6 = ?",
        "answers": [
            8,
            17,
            -1,
            15
        ],
        "correct": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 7 = ?",
        "answers": [
            12,
            9,
            18,
            5
        ],
        "correct": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 12 = ?",
        "answers": [
            35,
            27,
            40,
            32
        ],
        "correct": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 11 = ?",
        "answers": [
            23,
            22,
            13,
            29
        ],
        "correct": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 15 = ?",
        "answers": [
            19,
            22,
            31,
            18
        ],
        "correct": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 19 = ?",
        "answers": [
            36,
            33,
            35,
            39
        ],
        "correct": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 15 = ?",
        "answers": [
            17,
            9,
            14,
            8
        ],
        "correct": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 5 = ?",
        "answers": [
            13,
            19,
            18,
            20
        ],
        "correct": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 4 = ?",
        "answers": [
            27,
            14,
            24,
            17
        ],
        "correct": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 16 = ?",
        "answers": [
            11,
            13,
            21,
            25
        ],
        "correct": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 8 = ?",
        "answers": [
            9,
            3,
            12,
            11
        ],
        "correct": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 6 = ?",
        "answers": [
            2,
            7,
            6,
            0
        ],
        "correct": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 7 = ?",
        "answers": [
            10,
            18,
            12,
            26
        ],
        "correct": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 14 = ?",
        "answers": [
            29,
            26,
            16,
            21
        ],
        "correct": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 6 = ?",
        "answers": [
            13,
            14,
            9,
            12
        ],
        "correct": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 11 = ?",
        "answers": [
            7,
            18,
            10,
            12
        ],
        "correct": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 2 = ?",
        "answers": [
            1,
            5,
            10,
            4
        ],
        "correct": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 11 = ?",
        "answers": [
            24,
            31,
            40,
            35
        ],
        "correct": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 19 = ?",
        "answers": [
            46,
            32,
            39,
            42
        ],
        "correct": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 10 = ?",
        "answers": [
            23,
            19,
            26,
            18
        ],
        "correct": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 4 = ?",
        "answers": [
            14,
            10,
            17,
            15
        ],
        "correct": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 14 = ?",
        "answers": [
            28,
            23,
            17,
            27
        ],
        "correct": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 15 = ?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            30,
            28,
            38
        ],
        "correct": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 7 = ?",
        "answers": [
            17,
            25,
            15,
            14
        ],
        "correct": 15
    }
]